Share with you my full stock list and
watchlist that I'm looking at. This right
here, this website, which if you purchase,
you already have access, so just check
your email. You should have a member's
number and you should be able to sign in
with your email to access the full list.
If not, you have an issues, email me. Your
payment receipt or your screenshot. Now
make sure that you get access and can get
access. But this is the website that's for
members only. Either you purchase the
video and you are a member or you are
already a member for INNERG, the whole
ecosystem. This is where the financial
information will be at. What will be on
here will be the Movers of the Week. So it
will always be updated with the ones that
have moved the most in one week period. If
you don't have a broker's account yet and
you're watching this video and you're
saying, well, where can I get one?
Robinhood, Invite. If you use that link,
the referral link, we both can get free
stocks or free shares of a stock. So if
you're not ready to invest your money yet
and you still want to be exposed, you
still want to be an investor, still want
to have the account, sign up with this
referral link and we both will get a piece
of shares, right? Free, you know, none of
our own money. So if that's you and you're
ready to invest without spending your own
money, sign up, use that link and both of
us will get some shares, right? That can
be your starting point to being an
investor. Who knows what share you have,
but it'll be shares that you own as a real
-life human and those will be real shares
that you have into that company. You can
sell it, you can keep it, but you will now
have on boarded the venture being an
investor, right? Here's where you create
the account. Again, if you already paid,
you have access. If not, pretty much it
would be a revolving subscription, right?
So if you paid the one time for the video,
you get an access, but if you're a member,
you are paying that $10 a month
subscription, simply because you are
getting more stuff
for...
Yeah, I may actually change that. So it
may not be $10 per month. So whatever
you're watching this, if it's $10 a month,
you locked in, contact me so we can make
sure just one... I don't think I want to
do this subscription thing. All right, so
one time price for the video, one time
price for admission and you're a member.
All right, that's cool with y'all. If
that's cool with y'all, like this video,
share and let me know. All right, so once
you're a member though and you have access
to this website, these are the platforms
I'm investing in right now. I'm currently
focused on AI and computation, meaning
these AI data centers, storage,
technology, the materials being made to
create these devices and stuff, right?
Platforms and FinTech, oh, I'm sorry. So
these companies like ARM Holdings, Marvel
Technologies, CoreWeave, Western Digital,
they will create the chips and the storage
for these places for today and just
continuing on. Like why would they not?
With the economy and type of advancements
we are growing into. Platforms and
FinTech, those are of course the big dogs,
companies that are controlling these
rails. So my favorites are Hood right now,
Robinhood, and Opendoor Technologies.
Those are two ones that I am focused on
right now. And in crypto, these are crypto
coins on a blockchain. So you will not
find these crypto coins on a brokerage
accounts if they offer crypto, but if not,
this crypto is not a stock. So you have to
go on a blockchain, you have to get a
blockchain wallet and have crypto money to
be able to purchase these crypto coins.
All right, energies and commodities, of
course, our natural resources will always
be something. And that is oil, petroleum,
these things that have been going on for a
long time, look, all green. 30 days, 22,
14, 10. So as you can see, these are for
over 30 days, your return is 22%, 14% over
30 days. Now, if you look at the one week
or the one day, it may not be as much. But
remember what I said.